const principlesOfAnimations_questions = [
  {
    question: "What is essential to create animations with the illusion of gravity, weight, mass, and flexibility?",
    answer: "Squash and Stretch",
    category: "principlesOfAnimations"
  },
  {
    question: "What helps to prepare the viewer for what's about to happen, making any motion feel real?",
    answer: "Anticipation",
    category: "principlesOfAnimations"
  },
  {
    question: "What describes motions that guide the viewer's eye and draw attention to what's important within the scene?",
    answer: "Staging",
    category: "principlesOfAnimations"
  },
  {
    question: "What refers to two different approaches to animation, with one drawing frame-by-frame from start to finish?",
    answer: "Straight-Ahead Action and Pose to Pose",
    category: "principlesOfAnimations"
  },
  {
    question: "What reflects the fact that not all parts of an object move at the same time?",
    answer: "Follow Through and Overlapping Action",
    category: "principlesOfAnimations"
  },
  {
    question: "What defines how movement starts and stops, with examples like a vehicle starting to move slowly before accelerating?",
    answer: "Slow In and Slow Out",
    category: "principlesOfAnimations"
  },
  {
    question: "In the physical world, how do most objects move?",
    answer: "Arc",
    category: "principlesOfAnimations"
  },
  {
    question: "What are used to support or emphasize the main action going on within a scene, adding another dimension to animations?",
    answer: "Secondary Action",
    category: "principlesOfAnimations"
  },
  {
    question: "What gives animations a fun character and helps the viewer focus on what’s important?",
    answer: "Exaggeration",
    category: "principlesOfAnimations"
  },
  {
    question: "Understanding the basics of drawing—or, in the case of UI, the principles of visual design—will help designers create more successful animations. What principle does this refer to?",
    answer: "Solid Drawing",
    category: "principlesOfAnimations"
  },
  {
    question: "What do animations need to do in order to trigger the viewer's attention and create a pull?",
    answer: "Appeal",
    category: "principlesOfAnimations"
  }
];

export default principlesOfAnimations_questions;
